buttons feel like real buttons it's kind
of something you have to experience in
order to really understand now the
benefit of touch response is that you
really have to click in on a button in
order to get it to register as a
physical click like you would with a
physical button and if you graze an icon
you don't necessarily go into that
portion of the menu that's good because
when you're driving you don't get false
positives as you're sort of bumping
along the road but if you prefer a
lighter touch you can turn off touch
response in a menu now along the edge
closest to the driver you have five
shortcuts that are customizable and they
are pretty much consistent they'll be
here no matter where you go in the
interface if you pop into the map
they'll be there if you go into the
radio they'll be there as well the rest
of the interface uses large icons that
are very easy to click and one of the
things that I really like about the
system is that it's customizable if you
don't like the order that things are in
you can touch and hold and then just